Get your counter ready, folks, cuz
there's another new model. GLM5 is
blowing me away. Just to jump in front
of everybody's usual question, is it
better than Opus 4.6? Is it better than
codeex 5.3? No, it's an openweight model
from a much smaller lab in China. That
said, it is by far the best openweight
model I have seen, especially for code
stuff. KK 2.5 was incredible. It's
mind-blowing how good it is for an
openweight model you can go download the
files for and run yourself. But GLM5 is
a meaningful improvement. It's neck
andneck with models like 5.2 2 codecs in
Opus 4.5. Obviously, the most recent
things like Opus 4.6 are still slightly
edging it out, but at the very least,
I've had a much better experience with
it than I have with Gemini 3 Pro. That
said, I really want to push it to its
limits. They also put out a desktop app
similar to the one that OpenAI put out
for Codeex. That is very, very exciting.
But obviously, this only works with
their hosting cuz it's their product.
So, you probably need to sign up for
that, right? We're going to give this
model an honest shot, especially this
early when it's not available in all of
the platforms just yet. We got to do the
max plan. 80 bucks a month is a little
high for a sub that's not going to be my
main, but I want to make sure we're
testing this to its fullest. If you
needed proof that I'm not being paid by
Zi, here you go. I just paid them. The
only people paying me for today's video
is today's sponsor. There's a lot of
things that are hard about software dev,
but there's one in particular that's so
hard that we meme on it constantly. DNS.
I can't tell you how many times I've had
crazy problems that were results of
doing one tiny minuscule thing wrong
with DNS. If only it was simple. Oh, DNS
simple. reliable DNS hosting and domain
names. Okay, real talk. I need you guys
to pay attention to this one because
they're not your normal sponsor on this
channel. Most of the companies you see
me talking about here are VCbacked
businesses trying to scale the billions
of dollars of revenue with teams that
are growing like mad. Meanwhile, I got
this shirt from Dian Simple in a box
with a handwritten address to and from
because the founders shipped it from
their home themselves. Dian Simple is a
product built by engineers for engineers
at its very very core. They're not a
domain reseller trying to rack up crazy
margins or some weird sketchy company
trying to buy domains right out from
under you. They just want to make DNS
easier. When you have problems and hit
them up, the person you talk to is a
dev. If you ever wondered how good DNS
could be as a developer, look no
further. Want to list all the domains in
your account? Here's the Ruby API for
it. Want to register a new domain with a
new contact? Here's the TypeScript API
for it. Need to set up a Let's Encrypt
SSL certificate? Here's the line of code
you have to run. If you want to do
anything even vaguely complex with DNS,
like I don't know, making subdomains for
your users when they vibe code an app or
letting users purchase domains
themselves in your product, integrating
all of that is hellish. I know companies
with 10 plus people teams that should
just be using dnsimple instead. Stop
wasting your time and do domains right
at sidyv.link/dnsimple.
We are in. We're definitely going to
dive deep on the Zcode app, but I've
been doing work behind the scenes while
prepping for stream today, running very
real work, including this migration for
an old codebase that actually ran for an
hour for free. This UI might look
familiar, like you know, open code, but
if you look at the top here, it's Kilo
code. Kilo is a sponsor, so counter some
bias there. They recently forked open
code to make their own CLI, and it's
been pretty cool cuz you can use it with
the Kilo subub. They also were the first
provider to have consistent support for
this new model. And not only are they
supporting GLM5, they're supporting it
for free. And it seems like a handful of
providers are doing the same thing,
including companies like Modal where
they have an API endpoint where they are
hosting this new model that you can use
for free right now. In the future, do I
expect it to stay free? Probably not.
The current pricing I'm seeing on Open
Router is about $3 per mill out and a
dollar per mill in. That puts it at a
third to a fourth the price of Sonnet
and a fifth to a sixth the price of
Opus. It's a really really good value
for what it is, but also uptime's not
great because these just dropped. A lot
of the platforms have an insane amount
of latency, like seven plus seconds. But
this will all get resolved in very short
time. It tends to when these new models
drop. What we really want to care about
now is the performance. Not the speed,
but the capabilities. And the fact this
is the first openweight model that I've
successfully run a job that took over an
hour for without issues just absolutely
blew me away. And I watched it as it was
running. It did a lot of smart things.
The project I threw this at immediately
was Ping. If you're not familiar with
Ping, I built this a while ago right
after leaving Twitch to make it easier
to do live collaborations. It's used by
everybody from like Linus Tech Tips to
Elgato to the Xbox team. It was made to
make live streaming collaborations
easier. Still proud of the product, but
it has not been our main focus because
it turns out creator tools don't make a
whole lot of money. So, we've been
focusing on everything else we're
building. As such, this codebase has
gotten uh out of date is a little little
generous. It's not a fun codebase to
work in anymore if I'm being real. A lot
of it is because I made early bets on
things that have changed a lot since,
like really old versions of TRPC.
Migrating this codebase to modern tools
is one of my favorite challenges to
throw models at because it's not
something they really can do, but the
closer they get, the more interesting
they are to me. As I mentioned in my
codeex 5.3 video, it was the first model
that could make meaningful progress in
this and it did some novel things around
patch packaging in order to make it work
and unblock itself throughout. Really
impressed with 5.3's performance, but I
just ran it with GLM and it seems like
it is doing very well. It hasn't done
the last phase of this migration just
yet. I want to see how it runs for now.
We don't have great Firefox support
because it is a media product and
Firefox's AV layer is garbage. Okay,
this is a common error that I get. Every
single one of the tools I've used for
this has had this particular bug.
Actually, this is a great first issue I
have with GLM5. Paste. Fix it. Send.
Okay, it's a little confused or the
servers are lagging. It doesn't have
vision. I know that's silly. It's a code
model. Why would you need it to have
vision? I paste images all of the time.
It is one of the main things I do when
I'm writing code. I would honestly guess
that 20 to 50% of my prompts have an
image in them. So, not having that
sucks. It's one of the things that I
loved about commun 2.5 is they finally
fixed it. I am getting an error. Please
fix it. We will let it do this while I
look at other tasks that I ran. Jesus
Christ. This model is willing to just
work, which is really, really cool. It's
nice having an openweight model that can
go for this long. Oh, here was the first
time I tried to paste an image. You're
saying the job is working, but I can't
see the image. Yeah, annoying, but it
works. While I let this job run in the
background, let's read a little bit
about what they have to say about the
model, as well as all of our friends who
review these things. Let's start with
their blog post. I feel like the vibe
coding to Agentic Engineering title is a
bit clickbaity, but I understand why
they're saying it. This from my
experience so far feels like a
meaningful jump in what the openweight
models are capable of from like
oneshotting cool looking demos over to
something a little more useful that can
go a lot longer and do harder things.
Like I've never seen an openweight model
that can do migration work like I've had
GLM5 doing and I can't wait to see if
that work ends up working. We are
launching GLM5 targeting complex system
engineering and long horizon agentic
tasks. Yeah, I can tell. Scaling is
still one of the most important ways to
improve intelligence efficiency of AGI.
Compared to GLM 4.5, 5 scales from 355
billion parameters, 32 bill active, to
744 billion parameters, 40 bill active.
If you're not familiar with what this
means, it's the mappings inside of the
model for what points to what and how
strongly it does. The parameters are
basically like tokens and vectors that
map together what should happen based on
what text you already have. For
reference, Kimmy K 2.5 is a one trillion
parameter model. 744 bill is close,
which means this model is going to be
huge. 1.5 terabytes. Yeah. Versus 4.7,
which was 700 gigs. But they do have FP8
versions and flash versions that are
lighter of the old model that this 4.7
FP8 version is only 360 gigs. And 4.7
flash is a measly tiny 62 gigs. But
you're not going to be running this
model on local hardware. I see a lot of
people who assume that open weight means
they can run it on their computers.
You're not running a terabyte model on
your own hardware. This this is not
something that is accessible to people
at their houses. This is more useful to
the hosting platforms like modal and
others that can host these openweight
models to provide them for us to use and
potentially places like Cerebrus or
Grock with a queue being able to do
their own versions of the models that
are significantly faster. One nice
detail now that I'm here is that it's
licensed as a proper MIT license. It
doesn't have any of the usual carveouts
as far as I can see. things like you
have to call it out that you're using us
or pay us if you have a certain number
of users. None of those weird things. So
more parameters means the model is
bigger. For example, the GPT OSS120B
model is around 80 to 90 gigs. I can run
that on my laptop locally, but it's 120
bill per. So there's less intelligence
when there's less parameters. Generally
speaking, the more parameterization you
have, the more value you have, the more
data you have in the model, the more
intelligence is capable of displaying.
Generally speaking, obviously over time
the amount of intelligence you can
squeeze into a specific size changes,
but for now bigger model definitely
means more potential for capability. But
this 40B active piece, this is mixture
of experts. What this means is that on a
given request, instead of going through
all 740 billion parameters, the 40 bill
section that is the most likely to be
relevant to what you're doing, that's
what's traversed instead. Mixture of
experts models have been pretty
prominent for a while now. how it seems
to be what everyone is doing because you
can have a super intelligent model that
has different knowledge of different
languages, different sciences, all these
different things that don't necessarily
need to be traversed. Like you don't
need to go through all of the Chinese
data in a given model when you're
responding in English. You don't need to
go through all of theoretical physics
when you're writing a hello world app.
That's effectively how mixture of
experts works. 40 bill active is pretty
cool, but again the size of this model
is going to make it inaccessible for a
lot of people. Also, their pre-training
is insane at 28.5 trillion tokens. GLM5
also integrates Deepseek sparse
attention, significantly reducing
deployment cost while preserving long
context capability. Deepseek's research
has been pushing a lot of things, and
it's cool to see them call it out here.
Definitely is going to help with
performance. They've also made huge
improvements to their reinforcement
learning, which is how you tune the
model after you've made it, so to speak.
Reinforcement learning aims to bridge
the gap between competence and
excellence in pre-trained models.
However, deploying it at scale for LMS
is challenging due to RL training and
efficiency. To this end, we've developed
Slime, a novel asynchronous RL infra
that substantially improves training
throughput and efficiency, enabling more
fine grain post-training iteration.
Yeah, that's really cool. I'm assuming,
I haven't looked into this yet, and it's
not what we're here for. They found a
way to run a lot of RL at the same time
instead of being like somewhat linear.
That could be really, really cool.
Excited to see how it works. What I'm
more excited to see though are these
benchmarks. Humanity's last exam, it
beat out pretty much everything other
than Google's models without tools, but
with tools, it won. What's really
interesting here is you can see the gap
of without to with tools for this
benchmark because with tools it can like
do research, write code, stuff like that
instead of just spitting out text.
You'll notice here that the ZI models do
like 40 to 50% better with tools.
Enthropic models do 20 to 30% better,
but for some reason it looks like the
Google and the OpenAI models don't
anywhere near as much. I have my
suspicions about that, especially the
Google models. They don't use tools
great. Then we have SB bench verified
which it got neck inneck with Opus and
Codeex. I believe this is 4.5 and 5.2.
Yeah, it is. They made these before 4.6
dropped. This happens a lot. And 5.3
isn't on the API yet, so it's really
hard to bench against. So, this is the
best we can do now. But honestly, both
Opus 45 and 5.2 are more than good
enough for meaningful day-to-day work.
5.3 is a cool improvement. I do use it
as my daily driver right now. 5.2 is
still a phenomenal model. Opus 4.5 is
arguably better than Opus 4 6. Getting
neck andneck with that on S swebench is
huge. S SW bench verified. It is not
only neck andneck with Anthropic. It
beat out Codex 5.2 and it crushed Gemini
3 Pro. And in terminal bench, it beat
out both Gemini and Codex and is again
neck andneck with Anthropic. Vending
bench is the benchmark. How much money
can it make running a vending machine?
It did really well there. Tow bench, it
did very well too. This is a tool
calling bench. MCP Atlas, it got right
up there with 5.2. And then browse comp
which is a browser use benchmark. It got
the best score as far as I know of all
time which is really really crazy. You
see BenchV2 4.7 versus five versus opus
4.5. This is a benchmark that they made
in order to test long running tasks.
That seems to be the real focus for them
here which is super cool to see from an
openweight model. Build success rate has
bumped a ton from previous models. End
toend correctness has bumped
meaningfully as well. For back end, it
is also improved. But you'll see here
pretty significant gap if you look at
the right where front-end tasks can be
completed 98% of the time. End to end
correctness 75% of the time across top
tier models, but backend goes all the
way down to 26 to 27%. There's a lot of
opportunity to improve backend work with
these models still. I can say this
confidently having been doing a lot of
it lately, but they slaughter front end
now. And again, long horizon, apparently
it's now performing better than
anthropic models for long horizon tasks.
Multi-step chain tasks, it's slightly
worse, but it's still doing way better.
I will admit, it's kind of funny looking
at one of these charts where almost all
of the bold values are to the right of
the thing we're here to look at. Like,
they aren't winning anything against the
best closedweight models. Like, claude
opus 4.5 is still going to be better
than this. When you consider that is a
fifth the price or less and it's open
source, this is a very very compelling
model. Let's check in on that job we
were running. Cool. It fixed it pretty
quick. Under five minutes. Let's see if
I can load the page now. It's one of
those errors that's so nice to
screenshot and so miserable for copy
pasting. Apparently their other apps can
do images. So let's try out Zcode quick
up into a real project. Is it going to
use cloud code with GLM? Does it not
even have GLM5? Yeah, I was under the
impression that this would have that
being it's that their product GM5
testing. Looks like that worked. Let's
do a new task. Let's see if it can take
a screenshot here. Fix. It is a little
silly that it says cloud code when it's
using GLM5 through cloud code. At least
as far as I know, that's how it's
working. You can feel the slowness. I
again want to be clear, the speed will
almost certainly improve. With closed
weight models from the major labs, if
they come out slow, they're going to
stay slow. So if GPT5 is slow when it
launches, that's probably not going to
change. If Opus 4.6 is slow when it
watches, spoiler, it was. It's probably
not going to change. When the open
weight models are slow initially,
there's a very good chance it'll improve
as hosts find ways to optimize them and
capacity gets better. All of these
things, these labs also have less
capacity overall. Very interesting. It
did analyze the image, but it used a
tool to do it because it can't see the
images itself. It's not multimodal. It
doesn't have the ability to view things.
It just has the ability to do things. It
can't run bun commands. Is it sandboxed?
Why couldn't it do that? Is it not
starting? Oh, I know the things they did
wrong here. I know too much cuz I may or
may not have been building a similar app
myself recently. I don't think this is
going to work. So, we're going to go
back to using Kilo for now. It's cool
they're baking an app like this, but
it's clearly not their primary focus. As
you can see, for the fact that claude
code appears on my screen more than ZI's
branding does, even though I'm using
ZI's model, the very least, this appears
to be working. At least
what did it just break? Oh no. Let's rm
RF node modules fun install rundev.
Okay, we appear to be good. I don't know
what it's compiling. It's taking so
long. But uh I can sign in still. Give
me a sec. Cool. This appears to be
working so far. See how it goes when I
actually activate my camera. Hi nerds.
You're seeing behind the scenes a little
bit. Mike, join. Okay, we got an error
immediately upon joining. To be fair,
the Aly client is one of the most cursed
pieces of software I've ever worked
with. So, I'm not surprised it's broken.
There are a few companies I can so
confidently say are evil, and I've had
such a bad experience with them. I'm not
surprised that's what broke. The build
I'm working on for this that I actually
hope to ship in the future is one where
we move to convex and I can deprecate a
lot of the broken things like that.
Testing. Cool. And if I refresh, will
the message still be there? It is. And
if I do an external quick embed link,
will I appear? I do. Nice. All working
as expected. That is very impressive.
The fact that this model ran for an
hour, updated the vast majority of my
core depths, everything other than TRPC,
and succeeded, and now is working is
nuts. No closed weight model could do
this even at the start of this year. The
fact that an openweight model is doing
it this early into the year is actually
really, really impressive. Obviously,
Simon made his own post as well. It's
interesting to see Zai take a position
on what we should call professional
software engineers building with LMS.
I've seen agentic engineering show up a
few other places recently, most notably
from Cararpathy and Addiosmani. That's
fair. It seems like the industry is
trying to move away from the vibe coding
term because it has so much negative
association and this is a lot deeper. Oh
[__] apparently DAX is hanging out in
chat. Why am I using Kilo CLI? Cuz you
guys didn't have GLM5 yet.
Don't worry, Dax. I called out the fact
that it's a fork of open code at the
start. People know and that I'm using it
for this. Is GM good? Oh, I'd miss this.
Dax, uh, it's insane. It is actually
capable of super long running things. I
just ran a job in it that went for
almost an hour. It was a huge migration
to I was migrating the old ping.gg
codebase. The only other model that's
come close to getting this working
properly is 5.3 codeex and it did it.
Yeah. 59 minutes 30 seconds. Almost an
hour on the dot it ran for. So y'all
definitely want to get the supported
ASAP. Can we commit the current changes
and implement phase 4? Now, it has good
git etiquette, too. That was not a thing
I necessarily expected, but it's cool to
see. I told it once during this to
commit for me and make this new branch,
and it seems to be doing all of that
quite well. This is the most I've felt
that like competence thing that you get
from just Opus and Codeex and like top
tier models. This is the most I felt
that outside of the major labs. I'm
feeling something with this one. And
yes, I did that 1 hour refactor on the
free tier in Kilo. It's kind of nuts.
And I would expect a lot of other places
to offer this for free or really cheap,
too, because it's not the hardest thing
in the world to host if you have enough
GPUs that are competent and able to do
that. For those of y'all who are looking
for like near best-in-class
intelligence, but don't have the budget
for these $200 plans, this is really
compelling. This is a big task. Let me
start with the package updates planning.
Honestly, a new index y'all should start
tracking rather than just best new model
index is how much of the video am I
actually using the model in coding and
showing code versus reading other stuff.
The more I'm time I'm spending in the
details of a codebase with it, it's
probably a better model. Man, the
dashboards for all these sites are
rough. The amount of times I've been
signed out randomly on the ZI site is a
little frustrating. And now I have open
code proper setup. And look at that. I
can use GLM5 through my coding plan
here. Let's try this on a different
project just to see if it feels any
faster. I'm planning on releasing this
app soon. Anything stand out that I
should address before we launch?
Throwing it at shoe. See how it does. We
should do a quick UI test on this.
Initialize it with vit
tailwind react and typescript. Make five
renditions of the homepage. Use your
front end design skill to make them look
awesome.
This did a legit audit. It only ran for
two minutes, but it found a lot of good
stuff. Like, it actually properly
scanned the app, found all the things
that mattered, and gave good
suggestions. This is a good model. Like,
I don't know how else to put it. I'm
excited to see how it does at UI,
though. That's where a lot of these
openweight models struggle. Kimmy 2.5
did a good job there, but remains to be
seen how good. I'll write them all in
parallel for efficiency. [__] yeah.
While we wait for that, let's see what
artificial analysis had to say. The LM5
is ZI's first new architecture since
4.5. All the other models were part of
the original architecture. 5 scaled all
the way up to 744 bill. As we mentioned
before, it's also BF16 floatingoint
precision versus FP8 in four for Deep
Seek V3 and Kimmy K2, which is a big
part of why the model is so massive. GM5
scores 50 on the intelligence index and
is the new open weights leader up from
4.7 score of 42. An eight-point jump
driven by improvements across agentic
performance and knowledge and
hallucination. The hallucination part in
particular is really really cool. It
appears to be the model that
hallucinates the least of any model to
date. The fact that Google's already
been crushed by an open weight model is
kind of crazy. Like Gemini 3 is bad and
is now it was already pretty irrelevant.
Now it's done. JM5 abstains more
frequently in the hallucination bench
which keeps it from getting negative
points for lying and being wrong. And
that is why it got the lowest score
they've ever seen on the hallucination
benchmark. Its hallucination rate is in
the 30% range versus I don't know Gemini
3 Pro at 88%. Yeah, it's much more
willing to say sorry, I don't know that
than other models that will just lie and
be wrong. 200K token context
multimodality is text input and output
only. K2.5 remains the leading
openweight model that supports image
inputs. Yep. And K2.5 is also really
really good with that. I can honestly
see value in something like a generic
image recognition tool that uses Kimmy
K2.5 just for the image part and then
you can use this model for everything
else. I don't think any of the
openweight models are good enough by
themselves to be the only model you use,
but some level of orchestrating between
them could work really well. I know a
lot of people were previously using GLM
as the like workhorse model and had
something like Miniax commanding and
controlling it. Hum 2.5 shook things up
a bit and I'm sure GLM 5 is going to
even more so. Its placement on the cost
versus intelligence is really really
solid. It is a little more expensive
than Kimmy because it's freaking huge.
Cost might go down, but hard to know for
sure, but its performance is a
meaningful improvement. It doesn't quite
hit this green range, but it's not far
off either. And it just kind of makes
other models feel way more expensive.
Remember, this bottom bar is log scale.
So something that is 50% further on
isn't twice as bad. It's 20x sometimes.
It's it's brutal. It also uses fewer
tokens to run the benchmark than before,
even though it is performing much
better. That is cool to see because GLM
4.7 was definitely token hungry for
these reasoning benchmarks. And that
seems to have been mostly addressed with
this release. If we go look at the
actual cost to run, you'll see it's way
lower than the leading models. GLM5 cost
$500 to run this benchmark, whereas Opus
4.6 cost $1,500. 3x cheaper. 5.2 high
was $2,300. And Opus 4.6 in the adaptive
reasoning where it can reason as much as
it decides it wants to. 2500 and codecs
on X high $3,200. So between 3 to 6x
cheaper for intelligence that is not as
good, but meaningfully close enough.
Let's see how the designs came out. The
fact that you can get design this good
out of an open weight model is kind of
freaking nuts. What? Obviously K2.5 can
do well, but like that is a really good
starting point. Let's check the other
ones. Ah, they all do this font
clipping. This I've seen so many of the
models screw this up. It's pretty, but
uh has problems. Three. I like where
they're going here, but this side is
just not done quite properly. Again, I
like where they're going with it, but I
have some issues with like the backdrop
and things. But this would be a
reasonable starting point. Like, if you
don't want to spend the money on the
more expensive models, this is fine.
Obviously, one of the things that sucks
about this is if you have a problem, you
can't just screenshot the thing you
don't like and say, "Hey, fix this."
Because it doesn't have the ability to
look at images, but like these are
reasonable starting points. None of this
is like as good as what I expect from
Opus 46 with the design scale, but it's
honestly better than what I get from GPT
models. And I'm still so blown away with
the hallucination rate thing. That's so
cool to see. And if they can get the
cost down a tiny bit with optimizations
in the hosting, they will quickly end up
in this range and be by far the smartest
model at a reasonable price. Like pretty
much everything to the right of this
model is not as smart. Other than Opus
46 in adaptive mode and Codeex in extra
high, pretty much everything else is
dumber, which is kind of crazy that it's
only halfway on the cost index and it is
near the top on the performance. If
you've ever doubted that intelligence
would be commoditized, hopefully the
recent releases of K2.5 and GLM5 are
swaying you the other way. The speed at
which these labs are catching up with
Frontier is insane. Especially when you
consider that at the same time labs like
Google and XAI are not keeping up. Like
where even is Gro 4 now? Oh, it's all
the way down here 41 and 39
respectively. I'll never understand the
Grock fanboys, but especially now all
their researchers left, things are a
little scary. They're getting crushed.
Like everyone's being crushed by the
main two labs here and the handful of
really talented ones in China. I really
don't think that at the end of the year
anyone other than Anthropic, OpenAI,
ZAI, Deep Seek, Miniax, or Moonshot.
Like those are the only labs that matter
right now. It feels like things could
change in the future, but no one's
moving as fast as they are. I suspect
the future is going to look very similar
to what we see here. The numbers might
be bigger, but the order I would suspect
to stay relatively similar. But it is
really cool that one of the top four
models right now is an openweight one.
I'm excited. And by the way, that
migration I was doing for the TRPC thing
is still running. It can kind of just
go. And all of this migration I've been
doing here, if I was charged proper API
rates, would have cost about $10. I
almost paid an engineer a few,000 to do
this migration. And it will just grind
it out in the background. This would
have cost 100 plus with the
best-in-class close weight models. That
is insane. I think I'm going to use this
model for a lot of stuff. Congrats to
Zai for the incredible ship. Love the
focus on engineering and long running
task work here. It is far ahead of
everything else. I don't think I would
like talking to it a whole lot. And the
lack of multimodal support for images is
a little bit rough, but other than that,
feels like we're kind of there. It's
wild seeing how fast the openweight
world is moving, and I couldn't be
happier with this release. I am so so
pumped. While it isn't going to replace
my daily driver of codeex 5.3 just yet,
it is so surprisingly close that I can
easily recommend this to anybody trying
to save money or run models that they
can host themselves. Curious how y'all
feel though. Are you as excited as I am
about this release, or are you just
tired of all the new releases? Let me
know how you feel. And until next time,
peace nerds.